Preliminary Guide to the North Carolina Poverty Project Records, 1983-2004 and undated (bulk 1986-1997)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession, 2007 (2007-0023), 3 boxes
  - University library holdings for books related to poverty from:
    - University of Alabama Birmingham (Box 52)
    - University of Alabama (Box 52)
  - Professional Curriculum Vitaes (Box 53)
  - Collected information on Universities in South Carolina (Box 53)
  - Collected information on Universities in North Carolina (Box 53)
  - Collected information on Universities in Alabama (Box 53)
  - 2003 Poverty Conference (Box 53)
  - Documentation of the Poverty Coalition, 1997-2001 (Box 53)
  - One 3.5" diskette (Box 53)
    Diskette has been removed from this box and its contents have been migrated to the server.
  - Instruction materials for Understanding Poverty Basic Course (Box 54)
  - Poverty Introduction (Box 54)
  - Collection of documents titled Seminaries and Ethics (Box 54)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1999 (Box 54)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1982-1991 (Box 54)
  - Clippings and photocopies of articles about poverty, and clippings of articles on poverty from the New York Times, 1997-2001 (Box 55)